const STORE= {
    questions: [
      { //Question 1
        question: "What is Lord Voldemort’s real name?",
        options: [
        "Tom Marvolo Riddle",
        "Tom Marvilo Riddle",
        "Tom Marvin Riddle",
        "Tom Ravolo Riddle"
        ],
        answer: "Tom Marvolo Riddle",
      }, { //Question 2
        question: "What’s the LAST line of the book, Harry Potter and the Sorcerer’s Stone?",
        options: [
        "“Goodbye, for now, Hogwarts.”",
        "“Harry, Ron, and Hermione looked at each other sheepishly and smiled.”",
        "“I’m going to have a lot of fun with Dudley this summer…”",
        "“Until the fall,’ said Dumbledore with a nod.”"
        ],
        answer: "“I’m going to have a lot of fun with Dudley this summer…”",
      }, { //Question 3
        question: "According to the Dursley’s, how did Harry’s parents die?",
        options: [
        "In a plane crash",
        "In a train crash",
        "In a bus crash",
        "In a car crash"
        ],
        answer: "In a car crash",
      }, { //Question 4
        question: "What does S.P.E.W. stand for?",
        options: [
        "Society For the Promotion of Elfish Welfare",
        "Society For the Protection of Elves and Wizards",
        "Support For People, Elves, and Wizards",
        "Sorority For the Protection of Elves and Wands"
        ],
        answer: "Society For the Promotion of Elfish Welfare",
      }, { //Question 5
        question: "What is Dumbledore’s full name?",
        options: [
        "Albus Wulfric Percival Brian Dumbledore",
        "Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore",
        "Albus Percival Brian Wulfric Dumbledore",
        "Albus Brian Percival Wulfric Dumbledore"
        ],
        answer: "Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore",
      }, { //Question 6
        question: "What is the symbol for the Ravenclaw house?",
        options: [
        "Raven",
        "Crow",
        "Eagle",
        "Hawk"
        ],
        answer: "Eagle",
      }, { //Question 7
        question: "Dumbledore has a scar above his left knee. It’s a perfect map of what",
        options: [
        "Hogwarts",
        "The London Underground",
        "North America",
        "Diagon Alley"
        ],
        answer: "The London Underground",
      }, { //Question 8
        question: "How many Sickles are in a Galleon?",
        options: [
        "13",
        "15",
        "17",
        "19"
        ],
        answer: "17",
      }, { //Question 9
        question: "What are the three cores Garrick Ollivander uses in his wand making?",
        options: [
        "Phoenix feathers, dragon heartstring, and unicorn hair",
        "Phoenix feathers, dragon tooth, and centaur mane",
        "Dragon heartstring, unicorn horn, and centaur mane",
        "Phoenix beak, dragon heartstring, unicorn hair"
        ],
        answer: "Phoenix feathers, dragon heartstring, and unicorn hair",
      }, { //Question 10
        question: "What is a person born into a wizarding family who cannot do magic called?",
        options: [
        "Muggle",
        "Half-blood",
        "Mudblood",
        "Squib"
        ],
        answer: "Squib",
      }, { //Question 11
        question: "Who gave us the Marauder’s Map?",
        options: [
        "Messrs Moody, Wormtongue, Sappen, and Frongs",
        "Messrs Moony, Wormtail, Padfoot, and Prongs",
        "Messrs Molly, Wilfred, Peter, and Phongs",
        "Messrs Matchstick, Winston, Footfed, and Trongs"
        ],
        answer: "Messrs Moony, Wormtail, Padfoot, and Prongs",
      }, { //Question 12
        question: "How many points is the snitch worth in Quidditch?",
        options: [
        "100",
        "150",
        "200",
        "250"
        ],
        answer: "150",
      }, { //Question 13
        question: "Who founded the Order of the Phoenix?",
        options: [
        "Remus Lupin",
        "Albus Dumbledore",
        "Godric Gryffindor",
        "Sirius Black"
        ],
        answer: "Albus Dumbledore",
      }, { //Question 14
        question: "Which brothers are supposedly the original possessors the Deathly Hallows?",
        options: [
        "The Percival brothers",
        "The Principe brothers",
        "The Possimo brothers",
        "The Peverell brothers"
        ],
        answer: "The Peverell brothers",
      }, { //Question 15
        question: "What is the LAST line of Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        options: [
        "“Harry nodded.”",
        "“The scar had not pained Harry for 19 years. All was well.”",
        "“Off to school with you, Albus.”",
        "“Life was good.”"
        ],
        answer: "“The scar had not pained Harry for 19 years. All was well.”",
      }, { //Question 16
        question: "What are Albus Dumbledore’s siblings’ names?",
        options: [
        "Alastair and Aubrey",
        "Antioch and Avrielle",
        "Aberforth and Ariana",
        "Abel and Ariel"
        ],
        answer: "Aberforth and Ariana",
      }, { //Question 17
        question: "Which of these characters mentioned in Harry Potter was a real-life person?",
        options: [
        "Armando Dippet",
        "Nicholas Flamel",
        "Sir Nicholas de Mimsy-Porpington",
        "Sir Patrick Delaney-Podmore"
        ],
        answer: "Nicholas Flamel",
      }, { //Question 18
        question: "Which is NOT a house in the North American wizarding school, Ilvermorny?",
        options: [
        "Thunderbird",
        "Wampus",
        "Horned Rhino",
        "Pukwudgie"
        ],
        answer: "Horned Rhino",
      }, { //Question 19
        question: "Who put Harry’s name in the Goblet of Fire?",
        options: [
        "Peter Pettigrew",
        "Severus Snape",
        "Cornelius Fudge",
        "Barty Crouch, Jr."
        ],
        answer: "Barty Crouch, Jr.",
      }, { //Question 20
        question: "What is Hermione’s middle name?",
        options: [
        "Jean",
        "Melanie",
        "Roberta",
        "Sarah"
        ],
        answer: "Jean",
      }
    ],
    currentQuestion: 0,
    score: 0,
  };